<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kuruhinashetty Community</title>
    <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kuruhinashetty Community</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kuruhina Shetty Gotras</title>
      <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/gotras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/gotras/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ಕರಹನಶಟಟ-ಧರಮದವರ-ಗತರಗಳ&#34;&gt;ಕುರುಹಿನಶೆಟ್ಟಿ ಧರ್ಮದವರ ಗೋತ್ರಗಳ&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ಪರಚಯ&#34;&gt;ಪರಿಚಯ&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ಲೋಕ ಕಂಟಕರಾದ ತಾರಕಾಸುರ ಮೊದಲಾದ 66 ಕೋಟಿ ದಾನವರು ಸಕಲ ಲೋಕಂಗಳಿಗೆ ದಾಳಿಯನ್ನಿಡಲು ಹರಿಬ್ರಹ್ಮರಿ ೦ ದೊಡಗುಡಿ ದೇವತೆಗಳೆಲ್ಲರೂ ಆದಿಶಕ್ತಿ ಪಾರ್ವತಾದೇವಿಯಲ್ಲಿ ಮೊರೆಯಿಟ್ಟ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ಪಾರ್ವತಾದೇವಿಯು ಸಮಾಧಿಸ್ತನಾಗಿ ಕುಳಿತ ಪರಮೇಶ್ವರನನ್ನು ಎಚ್ಚರಗೊಳಿಸಲು ಆ ಪರಮೇಶ್ವರನು ಪಾರ್ವತಾದೇವಿಗೆ ಓಂಕಾರವೆಂಬ ರತಿಕಲೆಯನ್ನಿತ್ತುದರಿಂದ ಜಗದ್ವಾಪಿಯಾದ ಓಂಕಾರ ಪರಬ್ರಹ್ಮ ಮೂರ್ತಿಯೇ ತಾಕಾಸುರನ ವರಪ್ರಭಾವ ಶಕ್ತಿಗೆ ಮಿಗಿಲಾದ 66 ಜನ ರುದ್ರರಾಗಿ ಆವತರಿಸಿ ಬಂದು ವೃಷಭ ರೂಪದಿಂದ ದೈತ್ಯರನ್ನು ಸಂಹರಿಸಿದರು.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ಆ ದೈತ್ಯರನ್ನು ಸಂಹರಿಸುವ ಕಾಲಕ್ಕೆ 66 ದನುಜರಾಜನು ರುದ್ರರನ್ನು ಕುರಿತು ನಿಮ್ಮಿಂದ ನಮಗೆ ಮುಕ್ತಿ ದೊರೆಯುವದು ಅದಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವಂಶಜರು ನಮ್ಮನ್ನು ಸದಾ ನೆನೆಯುತ್ತಿರುವ ಹಾಗೆ ಅನುಗ್ರಹಿಸಬೇಕು &amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo; ಎಂದು ಬೇಡಿಕೊಂಡರು . ಅದರಂತೆ ರುದ್ರರು ಅನುಗ್ರಹಿಸಲಾಗಿ ಪಾರ್ವತಾದೇವಿಯು ರುದ್ರನ್ನು ಕೈಲಾಸಕ್ಕೆ ಕರೆದುಕೊಂಡು ಬಂದು ಆ ರುದ್ರರು ಯಾವ ಯಾವ ದನುಜರಾಜರ ಶಿರವಿಡಿದು ಕೊಂದಿದ್ದರೋ ಅವರವರ ಹೆಸರುಗಳೇ ತತ್ಪುತ್ರರಿಗೆ ಗೋತ್ರಗಳಾದವೆಂದು ಹೇಳಿದ ರೀತಿಯಲ್ಲಿ ಪಟ್ಟಗಟ್ಟಿದಳು ಹೇಗೆಂದರೆ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ಶ್ರೀ ನೀಲಕಂಠ ರುದ್ರನು ಶುಭ ವರ್ಣದ ವೃಷಭ ರೂಪದಿಂದ ಪರಘಾಸುರನೆಂಬ ದೈತ್ಯನನ್ನು ಸಂಹರಿಸಿದುದಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ಪರಮ ಗೋತ್ರವೆಂದು ನಾಮ ಉಂಟಾಯಿತು . ಅದಕ್ಕದೇ ಕುರುಹು . ಇದೇ ಪ್ರಕಾರ 66 ರುದ್ರರು ಭಿನ್ನ ಭಿನ್ನ ವರ್ಣದ ವೃಷಭ ರೂಪದಿಂದ 66 ದನುಜರಾಜರನ್ನು ಅವರ ಸೈನ್ಯಬಲದೊಂದಿಗೆ ಸಂಹರಿಸಿದ ಕುರಹಿಗಾಗಿ 66 ಗೊತ್ರಗಳ ನಾಮಗಳು ಕೆಳಗಿನಂತೆ ಉದಯಿಸಿದವು.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo uses the excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/pkg/html/template/&#34;&gt;html/template&lt;/a&gt; library for
its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very
small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of
logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other
template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of
similarities in Go templates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313 Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kuruhinashetty.in/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
